I have some alarming news for
the folks heading to Venus.
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
今日はぁ 金星行きメンバー達に
ショッキングなお知らせをしなければならない
We found out that the rocket taking us to Venus
has a cargo weight limit of one thousand pounds.
実は 金星行きに使うロケットが…
重量制限500キロまでであることが判明したあ
What?
何？
そ それってどういうことですか？
What does that mean for us?
Will we all fit?
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
全員乗れるのぉ？
騒ぐなあ！
Pipe down!
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
That's exactly why we'll be
weighing everyone today.
そこで 今日はみんなに
体重を測ってもらうことにした！
Those who are unfit will be put on
a dieting regimen immediately!
たるんだ肉体の者には ダイエット義務を課す！
足を引っ張るものは 地球に置いていくぞ！
All dead weight will be left behind on Earth!
B-But—
そ そんなぁ～！ あはっ
How many of us can fit with
the thousand-pound limit?
500キロって… どれくらい
乗れるもんなんですか？
ふん… よく見ていろ
500キロのシビアさを
Watch and see just how severe that limit is.
Only five adults!
ざっと大人５人分だ！
Okay, so why don't we just cut you right now?
よーし まずあなたから
降りていただきましょうかあ！
Ko! Sama! Go! Summer!! Ko! Sama! Go!
Co! Sama! Go! Summer!! Co! Sama! Go!…
Wait. I thought you were going to Venus.
“あれ？ 行くのは金星だよね？”
よもやまさかのこんな日が…おぉ
To think that this day would ever really (oh)...
yomoya masakano konna hi ga... oh
Finally come to be (oh).
yatte koyoutowa... oh
やって来ようとは…… おぉ
からの～
And so now!
Karano
シロハチオウムはお留守番
Whitey, the bee, and the bird will all stay at home,
shiro hachi oumu wa orusuban
高井は高井は会社にステイ
While I-I, Takai-at the office will I stay!
takai wa takai wa kaisha ni sutei
行ってらっしゃい金星
See you off to Venus!
itterasshai kinsei
行ってらっしゃいませと そら
Just saying my sad goodbyes, hey!
itterasshaimase to sora
可愛い行には旅をさせてあげなければと
言い聞かせる
I just have to tell myself
kawaii ko niwa tabi wo
I must let my dear young Ko be free and take his trip!
sasete agenakereba to iikikaseru
行ってらっしゃい 金星 あ～
See you off to Venus, ahh!
itterasshai kinsei ah
行ってらっしゃいませと ほれ
Just saying my sad goodbyes, oh no!
itterasshaimase to hore
行く行け行かねばならず いけずぅ
I wanna go, I wanna go, but no I can't. It's so sad!
iku ike ikanebanarazu ikezu
ワタクシは涙飲み固唾のみ
I'll endure this hardship, I'll endure it all,
watakushi wa namida nomi
I'll just hold my breath,
katazu nomi
貴方様へはなむけの歌をラララを
お送り致しましょう
And I'll give to you now, with my final gasp,
anatasama he hanamuke no
the gift of song (la la la), okay ready here we go!
uta wo lalala wo ookurisimashou
ラララァ……
La *sob* la laaa...
“向こうに行っても輝くんだぜ
河川敷の俺達にも見えるようにな”
Go and shine in the night sky, shine so bright we can see you from the riverbank.
“こ こ こ こ
行様ぁぁぁぁぁぁあああああああ!!!!!!!”
Master Kooooo!
Chapter 171: "Diet"
Age
Male
Sex
User ID
Underweight
Normal
Overweight
Obese
What?! He only has three percent body fat!
うわっ 何これ！ 体脂肪率３％って！
You don't have anything left to shed!
もうしぼる余地すらないじゃないかあ！
い 嫌だぞ 金星は全員で行くぞ！
No! Everyone has to go to Venus!
Let's all lose extra weight to make up for Sister!
シスターの分もみんなで痩せれば
いいじゃないか！
Nino...
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
ニノさん…
You're right! Let's all start our diets today!
おう その通りだぜぇ
今日から全員でダイエットだあ！
Yeah!
おう！
But we should come up with a few different plans
to make sure at least one of them works.
しかし 方法は何通りか用意した方が
共倒れがなくていいなあ…
Anyone have any ideas?
誰かいい方法を知ってる奴は…
I do! I do!
はいはいは～い！ ダイエットのことなら
あたしに任せて！
Just leave it to me! I'll teach you all
about my amazing strawberry diet!
あたしのとっておき イチゴダイエットを
伝授しちゃうわっ
おお～っ なんかオナゴに
ぴったりのダイエットじゃなっ
That sounds like just the thing for us girls!
Strawberries are great!
イチゴはとても美味しい！
All right! Then the girls are going with that!
よーし 女子組はこれで決まり！
３食イチゴ食べて 金星に行くわよ～！
We're gonna eat strawberries for every
meal and blast off to Venus!
Yeah!
Strawberry! Strawberry!
-イチゴ！ イチゴ！
-ちょっ
おい！ そのダイエット大丈夫か～？
Hey! Are you sure that's really gonna work?
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
Huh?
おや？
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
Whitey...
シロさん
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
Oh, that's right. Today's that meeting
for everyone going to Venus.
ああ そうか 今日は
金星行きの報告会かぁ…
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
Oh, yeah.
ああ はい
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
I see.
そうかぁ… 本当にみんな
行ってしまうんだねぇ…
So you're really leaving.
It'll be a lot quieter around here.
ここも 寂しくなっちゃうなぁ…
そうだった… シロさんは“残る人”だ…
That's right. Whitey decided to stay behind.
We'll be back.
俺達… きっと帰ってきますから…
あはっ 何だよ 行く前から
帰ることなんて考えてちゃダメさあ
Come on. You shouldn't be thinking about
coming back before you've even left.
I'll try to help out however I can.
Let me know if you need anything.
俺もできる限り努力するから
何かあったら言ってよね
Whitey...
シロさん…
うっふふ… 私だって協力するわよ
I'd like to help, too.
Jacqueline!
ジャクリーン！
I'm an aesthetician!
私はエステティシャン…
My slimming-massage technique will give
you the body you've always wanted.
理想のボディーラインを実現する
痩身マッサージの腕も超一流よぉ
If you're ready to make the goddess of
beauty Aphrodite green with envy,
美の女神アフロディーテを
嫉妬に狂わせる覚悟がおありなら…
come knock on the door of
my salon, "Queen's Bee"!
我がエステサロン「クインズビー」の
門を叩きなさいな！
You mean you can make my already
perfectly-toned body even more beautiful?!
この俺の均整のとれた魅せボディーを
さらに美しくだってえ？
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
I'm scared! I'm scared of my full potential!
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
こ 怖い… 自分自身の可能性が怖い！
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
General Meeting
for Venus
Trip Discussion
Huh? You can lose weight just
by getting a massage?
え 何？ 指圧みてーなの
受けるだけで痩せんのお？
あっほほほ！ いらっしゃいな！ はっ
I welcome you to try!
Yes!
はいっ
おっしゃーあ！ じゃあ俺も女神さんを
押し切って 寄り切ってみせるぜぇ！
Okay! I'm gonna shove that goddess
outta my way and really shine!
あ～あ～ 何ださっきからヌル～い
減量法ばっかじゃねーかあ
What's with them all falling for those
lame-ass weight reduction plans?
ったく やる気あんのかよ
Are they serious about this?
Agreed. You have to exercise
to get fit, plain and simple.
同感だな やはり動かねば体は作れん
For example, even a single week of the "Boot
Camp" program can totally change your body.
例えば 「ブートキャンプ」などは
１週間でも体は激変する…
And I have some exercises that
are even more effective.
それに私なら さらに効果的な
エクササイズを知っているぞ
マジで？ 俺それやるやる！
Really?! I wanna give those a try!
Us, too!
僕達もー！
拙者 今日からシスターを
“教官”と呼ぶでござるよ
I shall call you Drill Instructor
from this day forward!
I see. Well said!
そうかぁ… よく言った
"Boot Camp" is for little babies!
Welcome to my "Rookie Debut" program!
Boot Camp
「ブートキャンプ」を超えた「ルーキーデビュー」
エクササイズに 入隊おめでとう！
Boot Camp
Rookie Debut
Did you know? When your body shakes, your
muscles are constricting and burning calories.
知っているかあ？
“震える”というのは筋肉収縮だから
カロリーを消費できるんだ
Add aerobic exercises like sprinting into
the mix and it's even more effective.
それに“走る”という有酸素運動が
加わると効果的だなあ
In other words, fleeing in terror is enough
to make your waist size plummet!
つまり 怯えながら逃げ惑うだけで
貴様もサイズダウンだ！
Save me, Blanks!
助けてブランクス～！
Chapter 172: "Another Objective"
Diet in Progress
One week has passed since everyone
began their pre-trip diets.
金星行き一行の
ダイエットが始まって１週間…
うーむ
全く減らんなぁ…
I'm not losing any weight.
Maybe Venusians just don't change weight...
というより金星人は 体重が
変化しないのではないか？
I never wanna eat another strawberry
for the rest of my life.
わしももうイチゴは一生分食ったわい
I'm used to eating less because of
Sister's training, but this is just—
シスターの訓練であまり食わんのは
慣れとるが さすがに腹も…
Growl
P-ko... maybe you should try
eating some other stuff...
Ｐ子… やはり何か他にも食べては…
ちょっ… やめてよね 決めたでしょ
１日イチゴ ボウル１杯って！
Stop talking! We decided to eat just
one bowl of strawberries each day!
But your bowl is always empty
by three in the afternoon.
しかし 午後３時にして
Ｐ子のボウルはもう空っぽ…
All you have left is the stems.
ヘタしか残っていないではないか
It's fine! We decided! Nothing but strawberries!
いーの！ 決めたんだもの
イチゴだけって…
Oh...
あら…
You know, the stems are still technically
part of the strawberry.
だったらヘタはイチゴのうちよねえ…
ふっ…
Hold on, P-ko. I feel like that's something
you probably never want to do.
待てＰ子 それはとってもやっては
いけないことのような気がする
うん！ 食べても太らない人に
この気持ちが分かってたまるもんですか～！
You don't get fat no matter how much you eat!
You could never understand how I feel!
-はぐっ はっく はっ…
-うわあ
Are you okay?
お前大丈夫かあ？
I know how strenuous your diet
is, so I came to check up on you.
無茶なダイエットしてるから
様子見にきたんだけど…
ん！ 何よ… ひやかしに来たわけ？
What? Are you here to mock me?
I might not look it, but I did get thinner!
これでも前より痩せたんだからね！
Your skin may be smoother and glossier,
but you're not any thin—
あんたなんて妙にツヤツヤしてるだけで
痩せては… うっ
うっははっ あんまり見ないでくれよ
Please don't stare.
Aphrodite herself is already jealous of me.
嫉妬はアフロディーテだけで十分さ
まあ 常に見られているようにって
ジャクリーン先生のアドバイスでミニＴなんだけど
すみません サプリ飲む時間なんで…
コントレックス村の湧き水
持ち歩いてんじゃないわよ
Get that Contrexéville spring
water out of my face.
Just by looking at him, I can tell he
lost at least ten pounds for sure.
ああ でも 確かにあれは
５キロは落ちてるわ
Was all my suffering for nothing?!
But no, I can't give up yet!
あたしの苦労はムダだったの？
でも諦めちゃダメ！ あたしの
金星以外のもう１つの目標…
I have another goal besides going to Venus...
うっ… うふ…
My "have that cute baggy look while
wearing his dress shirt" dream!
憧れの“彼に借りたＹシャツが
ブカブカ”実現のために！
Hey, did you pack on a few, P-ko?
あれ？ Ｐ子お前太ったぁ？
うっ うははっ は？
Oh, maybe not. I guess I just
got a whole lot thinner.
あ ちげーかあ 俺がスゲー痩せたんだ
ああぁ…
It turns out I sweat a lot more than others.
いやなんか俺 発汗が人一倍
すごいらしくてよお…
Here we go...
痛っ！ 何これ？
チャックみたいな背びれが… いっ
What's going on? Your back
feels like it has a zipper.
That's what happens when you go
to the spa in that suit of yours.
そんなサウナスーツ的なもの着たまま
強引にエステ受けるからあ
No, the goddess of beauty
just loves me that much.
いやー 俺は美の女神に
愛されてただけだけど？
P-ko mistook him for a spirit with a "cute baggy
look while wearing his kappa suit" dream.
“彼に借りた河童スーツがブカブカ”な
メス妖怪じゃないかと Ｐ子は疑ってました
Chapter 173: "Progress Report"
And on the day of the progress report...
Diet Progress Report
そして 中間発表の日
Spa team: Rec, minus thirteen pounds.
エステ組 リク マイナス６キロ
The Chief, minus fifteen pounds.
村長 マイナス７キロ
presents
A total of minus twenty-eight pounds.
合計13キロ減成功～！
That's amazing!
すごいのう～！
ふん…
Next, Sister's team. Um... where are they?
次はシスターグループ… は どこだ？
Have you seen them anywhere, Rec?
見かけなかったか？ リク
Well, I do remember hearing Sister's gunfire
and their screams for mercy every night.
そう言えばぁ… しばらくはシスターの銃声と
星達の絶叫が聞こえる夜が続いていましたよねぇ
うーん… あ！ まさかリアルに
全滅してたりして？
Maybe they've all been put
out of commission for real.
I'll go look—
俺 ちょっと見て…
心配するなリク
Have no fear, Rec.
Sister!
シスター？
That's right. We've been here the entire time.
そうさ 俺達なら… ずっとここにいたぜ
What?! You were hiding up
there under the bridge?!
なっ 何ぃ？ 橋の下に
潜んでいたっていうのかぁー？
おおお！ 完全に体が変わってるぞ！
Your bodies have totally transformed!
無駄な脂肪のない戦士の体…
It's a warrior's body. Not a
single gram of extra fat.
But you've clearly put on a ton of weight!
Did you hear that sound you just made?
でも絶対体重増えてんだろ それー！
降りて来た時 ズダン！つったぞ！
Don't worry, Rec. Or should I say, don't be afraid.
リク 心配すんな…
いや 怯えるな… か？
What are you talking about?! Anyone would
be afraid if they saw a neck like yours!
はあ？ 何言ってんだお前！
誰だって怯えるわ！ その首に！
It's true, we may have gained a few pounds.
確かに体重は増えたかもしれない…
But what we've shed is more than just fat.
けど 俺達が削ぎ落したのは
脂肪だけじゃねえ…
You two will probably never
get those masks off now!
お前ら もう脱げねーだろ その鉄仮面！
We've spent the past week
lightening and toning...
俺達がこの１週間 削ぎ落し
研ぎ澄ましたのは…
Our hearts.
心の方なのだから…
だからその“成し遂げた”みてーな顔
やめろよ！
Stop looking like you've actually
done something great.
Listen up! Well done in surviving my training!
全員 よくぞ無事に生き延びたあー！
Drill Instructor!
教官！ だぁぁ… がぁ…
くっ… お荷物を５つに増やしやがって…
これで俺の努力も台無しにぃ！
Now we have five anchors weighing us down.
All that hard work I did, for nothing!
P-ko and her strawberry team don't look
any different, except for their dry skin.
Ｐ子達イチゴグループは 見るからに
肌が荒れたくらいしか変化がないしぃ…
Sorry...
すまん…
Wait! If I shave off all my hair,
I might be like a pound lighter...
いや しかし！ 全身の毛を剃れば
0.5キロぐらい…
Maybe if I donate some blood...
わしも血を抜けば…
人間の魂の重さは0.2グラムらしいから
それを落とせばぁ…
They say a human soul weighs point-two
grams, so if I just get rid of that—
Calm down! Especially you, P-ko!
落ち着こうか 特にＰ子ぉ！
How are the diets going, everyone?
みんな～ ダイエットは順調かーい？
シロさん
Whitey!
Um, well... good for some, not so good for others.
ええ まあ 順調な人もいれば
そうじゃないのも…
I see. So I guess you'll be heading
to Venus soon. Congrats!
そうか 金星に行ける日は近いね
おめでとう！
Oh, I got you a little something. It's konjac gel.
あ これお祝いの差し入れ…
こんにゃくだよ
Thank you, Whitey.
ありがとうございます シロさん あ…
ははっはぁ… やだな 涙が出るなんて…
Oh, jeez. Why am I crying?
I wanted to see you all off with a smile.
気持ちよく送ろうって決めたのに…
いいえ 嬉しいです 気を遣って
こんにゃくだなんて…
It's okay. This is so nice of you.
It's a really considerate gift.
Chocolate?
え？ チョコ？
Huh? There's whipped cream in mine.
おいこれぇ 中に生クリーム…
Red bean paste here.
こっちはあんこが…
Whitey... what is this?
シロさん これ…
Well, you know...
だって…
I just can't handle being alone.
おじさん 寂しいのとか無理だからね
He was very direct about it.
きっぱりと言い放ちました
Chapter 174: "Muscle"
One week has passed since everyone finished
their conscription in Sister's boot camp.
「シスターズブートキャンプ」に
入隊した男達が
スパルタ訓練により タフなボディーを
手に入れてから１週間…
In other words, the secondary
sexual characteristics are—
secondary sex characteristics
Keeping
things
tidy and in
order
Keeping
things
tidy and in
order
え～ つまり第２次性徴とは…
Man, those muscles sure disappeared fast.
いや～ すーぐ落ちちまったなあ～
筋肉…
I suppose building them so fast means
they had no staying power.
やはり即席でつけた筋肉は
身に付かんでござるな～…
But I really didn't wanna stick
around in that boot camp.
かといってブートキャンプを
続けるのはな～
あは めんどいでござるよ～
'Twas indeed quite a pain.
Those two bounced back and now
they're even lazier than ever.
反動で超自堕落な生活に
なってんなあー… ん？
secondary sex characteristics
Hey, Tetsuro! Class is currently in session.
こら 鉄郎！ 授業中だぞ
Tetsuo's asleep, too.
Aren't you gonna wake him up?
おうリク
じゃったら鉄雄もさっきから寝とるぞ
起こしたらないかんじゃろぅ
Well... hmm...
あー そうねー
Hey, Tetsuo... time to wake up...
Keeping
things
tidy and in
order
おーい 鉄雄ー… 起きろー…
Hey.
おいっ
Keeping
things
tidy and in
order
ビクッ！
Muscles.
筋肉は…
Muscles are granted to those who desire power.
力を望む者に与えられる
Um... I was just wondering if you could read page
62 in the textbook. I-If you don't mind, sir.
いえぇ その… 教科書62ページを
読んでいただけたらなぁって…
チィッ
でひっ！ あいっ…
おお 大丈夫かリク
Are you okay, Rec?
Textbook? Heh. Stupid.
教科書？ ふっ くだらん…
What living organisms need
isn't knowledge. It's power.
生命体にとって必要なのは
知識ではない… 力だ
But I got some good sleep thanks
to this lullaby you call a class.
しかし 貴様の授業とかいう
子守歌のお陰で よく眠れた…
Now, time for me to resume my training.
さて そろそろトレーニングを
再開するかぁ…
Ah, I guess we should excuse ourselves, then.
ああ じゃあ僕達は失礼しようかな？
We would certainly be in your
way if we remained here.
ここに座っていたら
邪魔でござろうしぃ…
No, that's perfect. Just stay right where you are.
いや 丁度よい… そこにいるがいい
You losers of muscle!
筋肉を失いし者達よ！
You two don't provide nearly enough resistance!
貴様ら２人では ちと負荷が足りんがな…
Tetsuo didn't stop his training,
even after boot camp ended.
兄ちゃん… キャンプを抜けてからも
筋トレやめられないんだ…
あお…
He doesn't even talk to me very much anymore...
最近は僕ともあまり口を
きいてくれなくて…
えいぃ！ くはは… どうだあ
効いてるかあ？
So? What do you think of this?!
If you can't stand the pain,
better just get stronger!
苦しいのならもっと強くなるのだなあ…
自分の大胸筋とばかり話してるしぃ…
He keeps talking to those pecs...
Pecs, huh? His friends sure have neat names.
大胸筋かぁ… 何だかきらびやかな
名前の友達ができたんだな
Did you hear what he just said?
The kid's sick in the head for sure!
いやぁ！ 確実になんらかの病ですよ！
ゆうことが不健全すぎるしぃ！
うっ うん！ ふっ ふん！
I thought a healthy body was supposed
to come with a healthy mind!
健全な肉体には 健全な精神が
宿るはずじゃあ…
そうけ？ わしはむしろ見直したがのう！
Oh yeah? I like him even more now.
Not only did he survive Sister's training, but he's
still working out even now that it's over.
シスターの特訓を生き抜いただけでなく
脱退してからも
体を作り続けるとは天晴じゃ！
ふ～あ～っ！
You're a better man than before, Tetsuo.
男が上がったのう 鉄雄
Don't you dare touch my sacred obliques.
俺の神聖な腹斜筋に触れるな
What's wrong? Are you upset
someone touched you?
どうした 他人に触れられて
ご機嫌斜めか？
Fine, I'll give you some attention.
仕方ない お前とも遊んでやるかぁ
ふんっ！ ううんっ そらそらどうだ
腹斜筋め 効いてるだろう…
How do you like them apples,
obliques? Hurts, don't it?!
ははは 可愛い奴め
嬉しそうに収縮してやがるぜ！
You're so adorable! Look at
you contract with such joy!
ええええ！ 何この子 超キモイ！
He's so creepy!
secondary sex characteristics
ふふん ふう ふんっ ふう ふふ…
乳酸が溜まってきや… うっ？
secondary sex characteristics
I can feel the lactic acid building up—
How dare you disrespect me like that, Tetsuo?
何じゃ？ 鉄雄 今の口のきき方は…
Is that how you talk to your boss?
ボスのわしにきく口じゃないじゃろが？
ふっ… ステラちゃん ボスっていうのは
一番強い者だろう？
Stella... around here, the boss
is whoever's strongest.
Are you sure you're the boss right now?
なら 今ボスは本当に
ステラちゃんなのかな？
Oh yeah? Just try me.
ほ～お なら試してみるかの？
ちょっ どうしたんだよ やめろ鉄雄！
それにステラも！
What's wrong with you?!
Stop it, Tetsuo! You too, Stella!
You're not the boss anymore, Stella!
ステラちゃんはボスなんかじゃない！
You're just a girl with superior genes worthy
of accepting my seed and bearing my child!
ステラちゃんは俺のぉ… 最強の遺伝子を
かけ合わせるに足る遺伝子を持ったぁ
俺の子を産むにふさわしい女よ！
ふんっ！ 思い上がるんじゃないわ！
You're in over your head.
わしの遺伝子はシスターのもんじゃい！
My genes belong to Sister!
バカ… まだそんなページまで
進んでないでしょう！ やだぁ もう！
Physical Education
Hey! We didn't get to that page
yet! This is too much!
Physical Education
He seems to have brains as well as brawn.
力だけでなく知識もあるみたいです
Chapter 175: "Twin Muscle"
Tetsuo. I will prove to you that your muscles
are nothing but makeshift decorations!
鉄雄… 貴様の筋肉が いかに付け焼刃か
思い知らせてやるわ！
ふっ あっ ふんっ！
This is bad. They're both really serious
about this. There might be blood...
secondary sex characteristics
まずいぞ ２人共本気だ…
血を見るかも知れない
I truly fear one of them may lose their life today.
いや それどころか どちらかが
命を落とすのではござらんか？
くそおっ！ 俺達には
どうすることもできないのか？
Dammit! Isn't there anything we can do?!
Sister, get over here!
シスター こっちです！
Oh, Sister!
おおっ シスター！
You have to stop this
meaningless fight right now!
早くこの不毛な戦いを止めて下さい！
はっははっ… いいなあ… 青春かあ…
Nice! I did that when I was young!
What?! I've never seen a bigger
smile on Sister's face!
何？ こんないい顔のシスター
見たことない！
secondary sex characteristics
ちょ！ 止めて下さいよ！
あんたが育てたんでしょ ２人共！
Stop them! You trained both of them, didn't you?!
Wrong. I didn't do anything.
違うな… 私が育てたのではない…
The muscles chose them.
筋肉が彼らを選んだのだ
I completely forgot he was the biggest
muscle worshiper of them all!
うわあ 忘れてたあ！
この人が一番筋肉信仰の人だって
忘れてたあー！
うっは… 確かになかなか
やるようじゃのう… だがそこまでじゃ！
Not bad. But that's as far as you go!
You'll never defeat me!
おまんはわしには勝てーん！
Not with this sexy body of mine...
愛する男の為に磨き上げた この…
that I honed for the man I love!
ナイスバディーにはの！
ふっ… 身長を操れるのが
自分だけだとでも？
You think you're the only one that
can manipulate your height?
ふうんっ！ ううっ… ううう…
Tetsuo, don't! If your neck gets any
thicker, your iron mask won't last!
ダ ダメだ兄ちゃん！
それ以上首が太くなってしまったら
鉄仮面がもたない！
If your mask breaks, the people at
the lab will find out where we are!
仮面が割れて… 研究所の奴らに
ここがバレちゃうよぉ！
くく… 望むところよ…
Bring them on!
secondary sex characteristics
Tetsuo is getting bigger, too.
鉄雄もどんどん巨大化していくぞ！
I'll beat down Stella right along with
all those jerks from the lab!
研究所の奴らなんぞ ステラちゃん
もろとも返り討ちにしてくれる！
に… 兄ちゃ～ん！
T-Tetsuo!
It actually stretched!
意外と伸びたー！
His clothes also stretched just enough
to keep things from becoming explicit.
服もアウトにならない程度に伸びました
Chapter 176: "Sibling Rivalry"
ふん！ ああ～うっ！
うっ うわ！ まずい まずいよこれ！
This is bad! This is really bad!
んっ… こうなったら！ うっ ううん！
Fine, then...
はぁ？ 何やってんだ鉄郎？ 今更
筋トレやったって仕方ねーだろ さすがに！
What are you doing, Tetsuro? Exercising
now isn't gonna do you any good!
It's nice that you're trying, but—
気持ちは立派だけど…
I have to stop him!
兄ちゃんを止めなくちゃ！
I'm not the same as my brother,
but I have faith in muscle, too!
兄ちゃんとは違うけど… くっ…
僕も筋肉を信じてる！
If you believe in them,
muscles will respond in kind!
筋肉を信じれば応えてくれる…
So when I tell them,
"Thank you for supporting me..."
僕を支えてくれてありがとうって
感謝の気持ちを持って鍛えれば…
え… あれ？ ちょっとぉ…
Hold on!
おや！
ふっ… 行くよ 筋肉達…
兄ちゃんを助けに！
Let's go, my muscles.
We have to help Tetsuo!
Sister, is that?
シスター！ あれはもしかして？
I've had my suspicions ever
since boot camp ended...
ブートキャンプの時から
もしやと思っていたが やはりか…
As a bodybuilder, he's superior even to his
brother. And he can harness the Holy Muscle!
聖なる筋肉を使いこなす…
兄以上の天才ビルダーだ！
Is it okay if we just assume
this is all a daydream?
俺達もう白昼夢見てると思って
いいですかあ？
うおお～あぁ～っ！
くっ もっと力が出ないのか…
俺の上腕二頭筋よ！
Can't you give me more power, my biceps?!
もっと早く動け！ 大腿四頭筋！
腓腹筋よ！ もっとお！
Move faster, quadriceps! My gastrocnemius
muscles! Give me more!
Stop it, Tetsuo!
やめて兄ちゃん！
His muscles are so gentle...
なんて柔らかな筋肉！
兄ちゃん… 筋肉の泣き声が
聞こえないのかい？
Can't you hear the desperate
cries of your muscles?
What?
何？
Stella! I can see your underwear!
ステラ～ パンツ見えてるぞおー！
うぬぅ！
きゃ～ いけ～ん
Oh no! I'm so embarrassed!
Tetsuo, you're wrong!
兄ちゃんは間違っている…
筋肉は痛めつけるもんじゃない！
Muscles aren't something you should hurt.
They're something you love tenderly—
like a flower, like a lover!
花のように… 恋人のように…
優しく愛するものさ
No! Muscles are like lion cubs! They only grow
stronger by being cast down into the valley!
違う！ 筋肉はライオンの子…
谷底に落としてこそ強くなる！
You're wrong!
違うよ！
三角筋も大円筋も腹直筋も
みんな大事な友達さ
Your deltoids, teres major, and your abs!
They're all your precious friends!
No! Soldiers don't need to be
friends with their general!
違う！ 兵士達との
なれ合いは不要なのだ！
I'm sorry, but... it seems like they're
communicating solely through posing.
あのぉ さっきからあの人達
ポージングだけで会話してませんか？
I'll admit, your spoiled muscles look beautiful.
確かに貴様の甘やかされて育った
筋肉は美しい
But Tetsuro! Muscles that don't
fight are no different from fat!
しかし鉄郎っ！ お前の戦わない筋肉など
脂肪と変わらん！
Are you mortified? Then in the name
of muscle, try to breach my fortress!
悔しいか？
悔しいなら この俺の筋肉という名の
要塞を打ち破り…
Try to stop the commander, my cardiac muscle!
総大将である心筋を止めてみろ！
I won't let anyone insult my friends.
Not even you, Tetsuo!
僕の筋肉（ともだち）を侮辱するのは…
たとえ兄ちゃんでも許さないよ！
Hold on! Are you two really going to
get into a fist fight over all this?!
ちょっ… 待てお前ら
本気で殴り合う気かあ？
This is really bad! You have to stop them, Sister!
まずいです 止めて下さい シスター！
あんな体同士で殴り合ったら
ただじゃあ…
Just look at them! If they fight in this state—
まだだ！
Not yet! If Tetsuro really is an apostle of the
Holy Muscle, no blood will be shed here.
もし本当に鉄郎が聖なる筋肉の
使い手なら… 決して血は流れない！
The power that even I could not obtain...
私にも手に入れることの
叶わなかったその力…
Tetsuro... you alone just may be able to...
鉄郎 お前なら！
さあ喜べ… 俺の筋肉よ 戦いだあ！
Rejoice, my muscles!
It's time for war!
Poor things.
可哀そうに…
な？ は はぁ ち 力が抜けていく？
My power is leaving me!
Listen, Tetsuo's muscles. I know it
hurts. You've all worked so hard...
辛いよね… 兄ちゃんの筋肉達…
ずっと頑張ってるのに…
お！ まさか これは！
No! This is...
My muscles are fleeing into Tetsuo's body!
俺の筋肉達が 鉄郎の体に亡命している？
Traitors! You've betrayed me!
裏切ったなぁ 裏切ったなぁ
俺の筋肉達よー！
My muscles!
うああ～～ん！
Your muscles worked so hard for you.
兄ちゃんの筋肉は 十分尽くしていたよ…
Sister, what just happened?
シスター どういうことだ？
ふっ… これが筋肉を愛する者だけが
使えるという…
You've witnessed a power that only those
who truly love muscles can access.
The power of the Holy Muscle Revolution.
ホーリーマッスルレボリューションの
力… か…
うわあ～あ！
Hey, Sister. We're really tired.
I think we're gonna get going.
あの シスター 僕達
疲れてるみたいなんで帰りますね
I wish it had all been a dream, but Tetsuro
stayed that way for quite a while after.
全てが夢であったと思いたいのに…
鉄郎は しばらくこの体のままでした
旅の終わりに想うもの
secondary sex characteristics
Keeping
things
tidy and in
order
Keeping
things
tidy and in
order
Chapter 177: "Arakawa Open-Air Classroom, 2nd Period"
求めるだけの日々は過ぎる
Spa basics
Today we're going to take some clay and practice
proper aesthetician massage technique.
Spa basics
冬を待たずにはしゃいでる
Great!
There's only one thing you need to remember—
Fill your fingers full of love...
赤いコートに包まれる君
and squeeze that fat!
Try it out! Massage with love!
Massage with love!
さよなら迷宮days
気づけばThank you days
Massage with love!
Oh～ good bye days
Spa basics
All done!
With love!
旅の始まり想うもの
Spa basics
Yay! All done!
立ち止まらずに深呼吸する
Takai! Takai!
What's wrong, Rec?
Takai recorded some weird song onto a tape for me and then ran off.
ふたり明日を泳いでる
Yeah, sometimes people sing what
they can't actually say to others.
Next time, on 11 BRIDGE x2!
魚みたいに並び揺れる
Takai!
Illustration: Hiromu Arakawa
辛いNo thank youです
悲しいNo thank youです
Oh no～ good bye days
今日は粘土を使って エステティシャンの
手の動きをレッスンよ
はーい
ポイントはたった１つ
指先に愛を込めて ひたすら…
脂肪をこねる！
はい やってみてえ！ 愛を込めてこねる！
愛を込めてこねる！
愛を込めてこねる
愛を込めてこねるっ！
愛を込めてこねる！
やっは～！ できたわ！
愛を込めて～！
愛をこめてぇ～！
愛をこめてえ～っ！
いえーい！
へいへーい！
高井 高井ー！
どうした？ リク
高井がカセットテープに 変な歌を
吹き込んだまま 行方不明なんです
うん… 人は言えない想いを
歌に託すからなあ
次回 「11 BRIDGE×２」
高井ーっ！